inspirock.com 2019-09-12

# Privacy Policy • Inspirock

**Last Updated Date: 24 May 2018**

Your privacy is important to us. You’ve placed your trust in us by using our services, and we value that trust. That means we’re committed to protecting and safeguarding any personal data you give us. We act in our customers' interest and are transparent about the processing of your personal data. 

This Privacy Policy explains our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Data that we receive through our Services. Please read it carefully, and Happy Travels! 

  * Collection and Use of Personal Data
  * Personal Data that We Share with Third-parties
  * Your Choices
  * The Security of Your Personal Data
  * Our Policy Toward Children
  * Other Legal Matters
  * Questions?

## Collection and Use of Personal Data

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Services, to administer your use of the Services (including your Account, if you are an Account holder), and to enable you to enjoy and easily navigate our Services. 

_Account Information_. If you create an Account, we’ll collect certain Personal Data that can be used to identify you, such as your name and email address (“PII”). If you create an Account using your login credentials from one of your SNS Account or other Accounts, we’ll be able to access and collect your name, email address, profile information, and other PII that your privacy settings on the SNS Account or other Accounts permit us to access. This Personal Data is used to ensure the security and privacy of your information. Your Personal Data may also be used to provide you with a more personalized experience when using our Services, for example. 

_Trip Information_. If you use our Services, you may provide Personal Data regarding your travel plans, schedules, preferences, bookings, notes, attachments, and other such information. In addition you may provide Personal Data about other Users who are traveling with you. We use this Personal Data to provide better Services to you and to those traveling with you. This may include sending emails, notifications, messages, etc. containing reminders, advertisements, and deals relevant to your trip. 

_Personal Data Collected Using Cookies and other Web Technologies_. Like many website owners and operators, we use automated data collection tools such as Cookies and Web Beacons to collect certain Personal Data. For additional information regarding our use of Cookies and other Web technologies, such as Web Beacons, please see our Cookie Policy ([www.inspirock.com/cookie-policy](https://www.inspirock.com/cookie-policy)). 

_Personal Data Related to Use of the Services_. Our servers automatically record certain information about how a person uses our Services (we refer to this information as “ **Log Data** ”), including both Account holders and non-Account holders (either, a “ **User** ”). Log Data may include Personal Data such as a User’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, operating system, the web page that a User was visiting before accessing our Services, the pages or features of our Services to which a User browsed and the time spent on those pages or features, which third-party website hosted the Services that brought a User the Services, search terms, information a User inputs related to their trip planning, adjustments made to existing itinerary, the links on our Services that a User clicked on, clickstream, session playback and statistics. We use Log Data to administer the Services and we analyze (and may engage third-parties to analyze) Log Data to improve, customize and enhance our Services by expanding their features and functionality and tailoring them to our Users’ needs and preferences. We may use a person’s IP address to generate aggregate, non-identifying information about how our Services are used. We may use it to improve your experience with the site, for example, to automatically determine the start and end city for your trip. 

_Personal Data Sent by Your Mobile Device_. We collect certain information that your mobile device sends when you use our Services, like a device identifier, user settings and the operating system of your device, as well as information about your use of our Services. Such Personal Data may be used, for example, to provide an experience optimized for your device. 

_Location Information_. When you use our Services, we may collect and store information about your location by converting your IP address into a rough geo-location or by accessing your device’s GPS coordinates or coarse location if you enable location services on your device. We may use such Personal Data to improve and personalize our Services for you, for example, by automatically determining the best route for your trip. 

_Personal Data you give us about other Users_. You may give us Personal Data about other Users, for example, other travelers who are planning the trip with you. We should point out that it is your responsibility to ensure the Users you have provided information about are aware that you’ve done so, and have accepted our Terms of Use ([www.inspirock.com/terms-of-use](https://www.inspirock.com/terms-of-use)) and this Privacy Policy. 

_Other usages_. In addition to above usages, we may use your Personal Data to provide a more personalized experience, solicit feedback from you, for quality assurance, for customer support, to prevent fraud and scam, and to ensure proper operation of our Services. 

## Personal Data that We Share with Third-parties

We do not rent or sell your PII. We will not share any Personal Data that we have collected from or regarding you except as described below:

_Personal Data Shared with Our Services Providers_. We may engage third-party services providers to work with us to administer and provide the Services. These third-party services providers have informed us or the general public that they apply security measures they consider adequate for the protection of Personal Data within their system, or they have a general reputation for applying such measures. One example of this is if you request that a travel agent should contact you or provide assistance with booking. 

_Personal Data Shared with Third-parties for Advertising and Research_. We may share non-PII Personal Data with third parties (for example Google Analytics, Data Management Platforms), for industry research and analysis, demographic profiling, advertising, sales, marketing, case-studies, analytics, collecting feedback, monitoring, and other similar purposes. For additional information regarding our disclosure of information to third-party advertising companies, please see our Cookie Policy ([www.inspirock.com/cookie-policy](https://www.inspirock.com/cookie-policy)). 

_Personal Data Disclosed in Connection with Business Transactions_. Personal Data that we collect from our users, including PII, is considered to be a business asset. Thus, if we are acquired by a third party as a result of a transaction such as a merger, acquisition or asset sale or if our assets are acquired by a third party in the event we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, some or all of our assets, including your PII, may be disclosed or transferred to a third-party acquirer in connection with the transaction. 

_Personal Data Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others_. We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any Personal Data about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate: (i) to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas); (ii) to protect our property, rights and safety and the property, rights and safety of a third party or the public in general; and (iii) to stop any activity that we consider illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity. 

## Your Choices

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use and sharing of your PII and we’ll respect the choices you make. Please note that if you decide not to provide us with the PII that we request, you may not be able to access all of the features of the Services. 

_Opt-Out_. We may periodically send you free newsletters, e-mails, messages, notifications, and other communication that directly promote our Services. When you receive such promotional communications from us, you will have the opportunity to “opt-out” (either through your Account or by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail you receive). We do need to send you certain communications regarding the Services and you will not be able to opt out of those communications – e.g., communications regarding updates to our Terms of Use ([www.inspirock.com/terms-of-use](https://www.inspirock.com/terms-of-use)) or this Privacy Policy, communications required to verify and protect your Personal Data, for managing your account, or information about billing. 

_Deleting or Modifying Your Personal Data_. You can delete your PII and your Account by signing into your account and choosing to delete your account. You can also request us to do it by sending a request at 942 Oakes St, E Palo Alto, CA 94303, USA with proof of your identity. We’ll take steps to delete your information as soon we can, but some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records or as otherwise required by law. 

_Accessing Your Information_. Your Account will list all the plans you have created with us and you can download or print any plan you choose. 

_Other choices_. If you do not want us to collect location information, you may disable that feature on your mobile device. Similarly, your browser has more controls you can use to control what cookies and other information that it communicates with our Services. Third-party services (e.g. analytics services, advertising services) typically also provide control over their collection and use of your Personal Data. Please also see our Cookie Policy ([www.inspirock.com/cookie-policy](https://www.inspirock.com/cookie-policy)) for more information. 

## The Security of Your Personal Data

We take reasonable administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect the information that we collect from or about you (including your PII) from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Our website is secured with HTTPS. However, submission platforms that lead to our Services may not have the same level of security. Please be aware that no method of transmitting information over the Internet or storing information is completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of any information. 

_Cloud Service Providers_. Please also be aware that we may also use third-party cloud service providers that provide hosting, data storage, data processing, backups, data analytics, logging, monitoring, and other services pursuant to standard terms and conditions that may be nonnegotiable. These service providers have informed us or the general public that they apply security measures they consider adequate for the protection of Personal Data within their system, or they have a general reputation for applying such measures. However, we will not be liable (to the fullest extent permitted by law) for any damages that may result from the misuse of any information, including Personal Data, by these companies. 

## Our Policy Toward Children

Our Services are not directed to children under 18 and we do not knowingly collect PII from children under 18. If we learn that we have collected PII of a child under 18 we will take steps to delete such information from our files as soon as possible. 

## Other Legal Matters

_To what Services does this policy apply_. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any third-party websites, services or applications, even if they are accessible through our Services. However, this Privacy Policy does apply to portions of our Services that are accessible via third-party websites, services, or applications. Also, please note that unless we define a term in this Privacy Policy, all capitalized terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Use ([www.inspirock.com/terms-of-use](https://www.inspirock.com/terms-of-use)). So, please make sure that you have read and understood our Terms of Use before using our Services. 

_Revisions to this Privacy Policy_. Any Personal Data that is collected via our Services is covered by the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such Personal Data is collected. We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we’ll notify you of those changes by posting them on the Services or by sending you an email or other notification, and we’ll update the “Last Updated Date” above to indicate when those changes will become effective. 

_Links to Other Sites_. Our Services may contain links to websites and services that are owned or operated by third parties. Any information that you provide on or to a third-party service or that is collected by a third-party service is provided directly to the owner or operator of the third-party service and is subject to the owner’s or operator’s privacy policy. We’re not responsible for the content, privacy or security practices and policies of any third-party service. To protect your Personal Data, we recommend that you carefully review the privacy policies of all third-party services that you access. 

_International Transfer_. Your PII may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. For example, if you’re located outside the United States and choose to provide your PII to us, we may transfer your PII to the United States and process it there. 

_Responding to Do Not Track Signals_. Our Site does not have the capability to respond to “Do Not Track” signals received from various web browsers. 

_Use of Google Maps API_. Our Services use Google Maps API(s). Here is a link to their [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy). 

## Questions?

Please contact us at @ or 942 Oakes St., E Palo Alto, CA 94303, USA if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy.
